# ADRIANA GUERRA

adriana.luz.guerra@gmail.com 📞 +1 949 763 8167 (in) linkedin.com/in/a-l-guerra





#### SKILLS

- SQI
- VBA
- MS Access
- VB
- C#
- ASP.NET
- .NET CORE
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

#### **EDUCATION**

# UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, BERKELEY

Graduated May 2007 BA in Cognitive Science

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Leadership
- Teaching/Mentoring
- Troubleshooting
- Communication

# LANGUAGES

- English: Native
- · Spanish: Fluent
- French: Proficient

#### **ADDITIONAL**

**US** Citizen

#### **PROFILE**

I am a self-motivated developer dedicated to research and learning in pursuit of well-designed code. Working in a variety of fields, from SCUBA diving to neuroscience research, has helped me learn to see the big picture and given me the ability to interpret end user needs. I am interested in developing efficient code that is user-friendly and versatile in an environment that will challenge me.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## **Bubble Solutions, 2017 - Present**

Developed business management software for SCUBA diving centers using MS Access, VBA, SQL, ASP.NET, C#, and VB.NET. I streamlined the customer registration process through a registration form accessible by media device and simplified business activities such as course registrations, product purchases, and employee pay sheets by consolidating them into one user-friendly data management system. I am currently working on converting our student management tools into a web app for SCUBA instructors and dive centers.

#### PROGRAM COORDINATOR

#### Roctopus Pro Center, Koh Tao, Thailand, 2018

Reorganized and oversaw a SCUBA diving professional training program. During my time with Roctopus Pro, I developed a training schedule to maximize opportunities for trainees while minimizing redundant work for limited staff, developed Google Sheet and Google Script based program management tools to track training progress easily, revamped the out-dated website, developed HTML email templates, and oversaw social media and responded to program inquiries.

#### **INSTRUCTOR**

#### Sairee Cottage Diving, Koh Tao, Thailand, 2013 - 2018

Worked as a head SCUBA diving instructor at a well regarded dive shop on one of the busiest diving locations in the world. As a head instructor I was responsible for teaching courses of all levels, from introductory experiences to courses for aspiring professionals. My responsibilities included organizing diving trips, and mentoring interns while ensuring the safety of all of my divers.

#### STAFF RESEARCH ASSOCIATE

# Univeristy of California, San Diego, 2010 - 2012

Worked with the Research on Aging and Development Lab and the Swartz Center for Computational Neuroscience. My responsibilities included collecting neurobehavioral measures (i.e. electroencephalography, eye tracking, body motion capture, and behavioral tests) from typical and clinical populations subjects, analyzing data using specialized software, and developing scripts and protocols to test the accuracy of data stream integration from various data sources with varying sampling rates.

Additional experience available upon request.